good morning or evening or afternoon
wherever you happen to be watching this
I am gonna tell you a bit about what I'm
up to at the beginning of each of these
live broadcasts that I do at 8:30
Pacific Standard Time
every morning I am part of a technology
cooperative called together tech and we
are a solution slash tech cooperative
that is creating systems and tech that
are needed for collaboration on a
massive scale
we are currently concentrating on
bringing project holders together to
collaborate on un solutions for our
projects my project under that umbrella
what I am currently exploring is called
solution regimes and they are a
generative conversation that creates
real potential solutions we could
implement right now if we had 10,000
interested people and $100,000 I am also
with under under the solution raising
and interested in working through a
process raising of how do we actually
create many of the amazing ideas that
are generated in the solution raisings
so yesterday during this hour we had a
solution raising life online we talked
about mental health I was joined by Eric
and Kyra and Shiloh and we talked about
what we currently do in mental health
mainly were talking about students
society in general Oh strangely I feel
like that was the solution raising we
touched on Co vid 19 released on and yet
it was like instrumental and the reason
we picked that topic our my plan is to
do a live solution raising every
Wednesday morning I like to stick by 13
so it's sticking at the same time that
Kiera happens to be available to mental
health one at 8:30 in the morning
hopefully Shiloh and Eric and whoever
else are able to come and join to do the
solution reasons quite pick the topic
for next week but something about like a
unified a unified theory we're just
gonna help the unified theory in an hour
that's all like how we actually because
all the things are interconnected how do
you actually create solutions
gather with that interconnectedness I
just don't know how we do that within a
solution raising so I go we got to
narrow it down to focus a little bit
because I don't know if we know what we
do currently for that I don't know if we
know what a future would look like it's
actually random people who show up who
don't it's just like most of the topics
we talk about are things that turn off
my camera for a second I have something
in my eye
nobody it's assumed you try and get
something out of my eye all right and
back
so that is yesterday like I said we did
the live solution raising today I'm
gonna talk a bit about the secret of
life I like sounding good to go saving
the world I know the secret of life and
although I say it with a with the humor
that it is well-intentioned it's also
true I haven't necessarily as well get
into well get into that and then
tomorrow what I would love to do and
massively every us every Friday just
because I already have our tech together
tech board median slash idea cafe on
Fridays that I've yet to post in the
Facebook group which I said I would post
right away on Saturday after we had it
oops but I'm gonna post it right after
this so but I want to do a live coaching
session every week at some point in time
so I took a life coaching in ten years
ago I went into it thinking that I was
gonna be somewhat like a counselor and
help people figure out what they wanted
to do and the coaching that I took was
really just being a conduit for the
person's own internal guidance which
actually liked it was tapping into
supposedly something that I nine did and
whether he did it or not it works so I'm
good with it that he would turn off his
his right and left hemisphere I know and
he would download images and pictures as
the same thing sounds from his
subconscious which were more what's
thought of his right brain and then he
turned back on his left brain and be
like okay now let's decode these what
does that mean and so someone getting an
elephant versus somebody else is gonna
mean some
it's kind of like during Tremont Earp
rotation but very unique and individual
and it's your subconscious speaking to
you so it gives you the best advice it
is it is weird and nearly magical which
is why I wanted which is what I'll be
talking about today hello person good
morning hey James I'll call you James I
was like trying to say your name on the
other things like that's not good use
some counselling that's good
you're here tomorrow morning I will be
looking for whoever wants to follow that
reminds me that's what I was going to do
change it don't I did not I gave this
feel instead let's go to my profile
people can join in you can't from
periscope unfortunately nothing they
don't have a way to to take it that's my
pinch tweet I'd start rap pictures of
that graph there we go I'm live there
buddy wants to come join in online you
can do so there if you're watching on
YouTube on Jubilee saves the world by
meandering through life you can follow
the link in the description and
participate on camera so tomorrow if
somebody shows up who wants to do that
we will be doing a live session I
haven't done the veneers so I don't know
how it's gonna go but it's a free life
coaching session to help somebody get in
touch with their subconscious because
everybody has inside of them this isn't
something that only the elite have only
some people have everyone has their
subconscious here to teach them and
guide them that's why we have dreams
this is why we have all of all of that
so to like what I this is my experience
anyway once I was able to get in touch
with my subconscious and listen to what
it had to say every time it was the
perfect advice because no one could give
you better advice that like your own
intuition as a conscious so that's what
we're gonna do on tour oh and then maybe
maybe every Friday
if not I'll pick another day of the week
to do that today I wanted to talk about
like I said the secret of life what I
have found a secret life and what came
up in the Omega conversation yesterday
was Jordan Hall and John for Becky and
guy send stock I believe all have
I think they were the one to have the
conversation I might have been a fourth
person as well of this religion that's
not a religion I know it's definitely
John for baekje and entered Hall and
although I haven't actually watched
those they come up in conversation a lot
in the game peace space and so we have
this this concept of like a god that's
not a God that we that I really heather
has coined and what I call the universe
because it's like this non religion
because it's not something that someone
else can give you can only prove it to
yourself and there is no sacred text
there is no ten commandments that you
have to follow these and actually the
only way you truly know the truth is by
working with other people because
there's all of my experiences and I
don't know what is like law and what is
movable unless other people are working
through that process too and they're
getting the information they're getting
their life path and it's like what do we
have in common what works for most
people what works for people like me
what works for people like like you what
are like you can only know that together
unless you're going to start an old
religion and unless it's like God comes
from on high and and dictate something
to you and now it's Holy Scripture so
everyone has to follow it because if you
don't it's blasphemy is very different
than oh this came from inside of me and
it's my guidance for myself what did you
get for you and how do they match up you
can't have something like the ten
commandments of that right you can have
universally I don't think anyone from
inside of them is like it's okay to
steal and murder people cool that might
happen I don't know but it's definitely
not by internal guidance that those
things are right so but then there's
other things like the ten commands like
honor your mother and father and keep
the holy days this Sabbath holy that are
but really that that's the most
important thing you got going on okay
it's like all your mother and father you
put to death keep the whole like don't
work on Sunday or Saturday at the
so like my own internal guidance has
given me some weird advice that I would
never give somebody else because it's my
guidance it's my life and in fact it's
flown in the face of what society has
said for the very reason that I'm here
to not listen to oh I needed the lesson
on a massive scale to not listen to
outside guidance and listen to my own
internal guidance because I had extreme
extreme is probably a bit much
I had social anxiety and it felt extreme
to me exist the only social anxiety the
only body I have become best I know
other people had it much worse but I was
able to bring that down considerably
what with a lot of logic actually but
also with starting to tap into my
internal guidance once I came into
contact with this logical world that is
actually possible oh hi shadow god I
yeah I don't I just specifically don't
call it God although Heather call that
God that's not a God that's not a god I
call it the universe just because I have
I and other people have issues with God
so like I grew up evangelical Christians
so there's that's just the reason I get
slightly triggered by God because God is
is to me the connotation of an outside
force that somebody else puts criteria
on this thing that I have experienced in
my life is like I don't know what this
is but it's freaking awesome and you I'm
gonna argue with it all the time but you
can't really argue with it just like you
can't argue with the coab in 19 it is
what it is is it's we can only work
around it it's like all right I just
gonna keep giving me the same lessons
until I learn them it's gonna keep
requesting the same things as me until I
do them and yet on the stubborn person
so I argue and way no I'm not doing that
you're gonna add so it just keeps coming
back around I how about now how it now
will you do it and the more that it
proves itself the process of listening
and growing and getting the next the
next thing the more the more proves
itself to me which is why however many
months ago I felt confident enough to
start
putting myself out like I keep putting
myself out there in like a deeper and
deeper context or a more and more
vulnerable context even though the
guidance from three four years ago was
to do what I'm now doing like go live on
YouTube goal I have my Facebook was like
no that's no mm-hmm that's the scene
safe that doesn't seem like something I
want to do right now and I wasn't ready
then but it keeps it keeps coming up
some of my own guidance is those things
where it's like if it feels scary to me
I can't do it and other people it's the
opposite that they need to do right they
they leap and then parachute opens and
they they find themselves in a much
better world I know if I push through
that fear then I did it cost by nervous
system something so there's I have this
fine balanced it to walk through my
health conditions give me like a
different set of rules I also like two
of the things that that basically guide
our health are to eat good nutritious
food and to get exercise and it helps
your body and although I try to do both
those things to the best of my capacity
my guidance is basically eat what you
want and make sure you get enough
nutrients don't obsess about the food
we're fixing that together and for
exercise I have chronic fatigue which
means that exercise is poison for my
body which is like the weirdest because
it's the number one guidance you get
from every medical professional even
people who know who are experts in
chronic fatigue you're like well just
try to gradually increase your your
actually as everyone who has it is like
that is poison don't do that that is
what every doctor will tell you to do do
not listen it will destroy you and and
so who does a listen to doctors like
whose best guidance is don't listen to
your doctors mine
anyone really with chronic illness who
gets into their into it enough because
someone's going to give you the wrong
information and then you stop trusting
in the system and you start and that is
I feel what it's like collectively going
on his we're all kind of slightly not
trusting in the system as it's the only
thing we can trust in we live in
interesting times right now and we can
see how our
Collective intertwines nests affects us
all like it's not just about do I trust
my governments in the media yeah no I do
not but I also trust in a virus so I am
stay inside I are some math and biology
and this isn't far-fetched and there's
nothing about it that doesn't that
doesn't make sense we are really held
hostage by the biology of a different
species and the COPE at 19 I am in
Canada I'm in Vancouver and so I guess
I'm done with the spiel and I can
actually talk to you yeah yeah I'm gonna
put your comment about the screen so I'm
I'm just reading it in my head anyone
can see it whether because it's also
like YouTube versus periscope I'm
responding to internal guidance and
balance and it is like I said I argue
with mine all the time my guides are
sarcastic and I'm like really that's
what you want me to do you no no
thank you
and um that is what I need them to be
like I can't yeah with the god I was
raised with a Christian God was very
simultaneously very loving and very
punitive and whatever this God is isn't
it is loving but in a different way like
it gives me a lot of difficulty it gives
me a lot of of trial to suspend like
okay because if you don't take the
guidance when it's it like it's like it
gives you kindergarden lessons and when
you fail them it gives you great one
lessons and when you fail those it like
it just keeps pushing you through until
you get to the point where like you
can't help but learn it and it gives you
like just all the people and the
situations that are exactly what you
were supposed to learn and I miss it's
kind of like the secret or when you
start to pay attention to things they
start to show up in them in the world
like view but if you drive your own car
your own car if you draw your make and
model of car you're way more likely to
see all of the things that the same make
and model of the car everywhere else and
it's similar to that like I've had I
need this in my legs I'm gonna need to
go buy a popcorn maker
by this and then they just show up like
on the free shelf or in an alley or I'm
like that's weird because I don't have
that baby needs well I guess maybe
there's always five or six that are
there that I'm kind of looking out for
it says one of them coming about is
going to be but they wouldn't come out
about unless it necessarily was open to
it by just saying yeah that's gonna come
in and the more that happens the more
you start to trust in it you're like who
needs to buy a book or maker
I'm sure ones coming into my life but
over the last I guess two years cheers I
don't know what became before ayahuasca
I don't know don't remember oh I guess
just Kyle sees which don't follow him
anymore
not you don't recommend him but he was
exactly what I needed in my life when I
came into contact with him
I don't even quite remember how I came
in contact with him but he is who I
found an intelligent enough funny
charismatic speaker about like how to
follow these these kind of things so
what I got from him mainly was to not
care about my output to be like an apple
tree doesn't care about what you do with
the apples are worried about that
because if it would just stop producing
apples it just is there to produce
apples and so I'm just here to listen
and like listen to my guidance and take
the next step take the next step
include like I get long ago for my
guides I'm gonna look like a crazy
person until I don't I say things like I
know the secret of the universe I have a
secret of life what's sure you do who
looks like you do okay it's not I don't
live this a hundred percent all day
every day because he can I'm an
imperfect human who does health
challenges as I own addictions has my
own shadow side that I am constantly
excavating like Who am I and why am I
here and even though I think I know my
purpose I every one of these questions I
love how I have a list and hook followed
it are things I answer on a deeper level
and every time I answer them I get a
much better understanding of my purpose
and my people and myself and what I need
truly every time and those are the four
questions Who am I for my people what is
my purpose and what do I need and so to
me the secret of life is this magic is
God this source the universe it is
loving and persistent and somehow it
teaches all of us our best lessons and
simultaneously I did I don't understand
how it happens like it's not like it's
all there just to teach me right KO bida
we're not all hanging out inside just to
teach me we although I'm learning a lot
from it a lot from the world having the
experience that I've had for the last
few years both realizing that although
this stay-at-home guidance is 90% of
what I did anyway that 10% that I didn't
I do really miss it I really miss my
community I wasn't just there for my
kids this is like I really miss going
and seen in person real human beings and
their kids and which are real human
beings like the adults and their kids
and that older people um I miss eating
with them I miss finding out about you
know mundane things in their life have
that their work when Heather school went
to be able to go my kid to being able to
go to school that has been the hugest
impacts like Oh for five months I was
worried about two months but my kids
getting stir-crazy
like I don't know what to do I can't do
any of the things we normally do like
have a playdate asked for outside help
it's like every resource that we got set
up
doesn't really apply to this time this
thing and yet I am so impressed with how
society is handling this right now the
fact that we are staying inside I'm
still in awe of like really this is how
a cool I thought we would have just let
5% of the population die that's how I
would know if I got to vote I wouldn't
know but I don't even know if I would
have thought about staying inside like
oh we all just stay separate we all just
do a court order cool that is again my
wife 90% of the time like stains
away from all the sensory stuff I don't
do it because of virus isn't you know
bacteria in fact I'm not a germaphobe
unless I'm in a hospital or now outside
of my house and absolutely we took the
we went to Edmonton from Vancouver which
means we flew there and we flew back so
to the airport twice most times I was
like it's your motherís and public
washrooms don't touch things stop
licking things why are you my kids also
oppositional e defiance as her mother in
so if I tell her not to do something she
needs to do it and I have yet to master
the art of tweaking it into a should
instead of a shouldn't right instead of
like touch your face keep your hands
down don't touch the rest of your body
because then it's like don't touch your
face oh don't do this and for little
little kids up all of them have that
that's why you're supposed to figure out
how to guide them and the right instead
of like don't touch that dude like yours
here's a toy to play with because none
of us react very well to no but anyway
back to the list by the secrets of life
is that piece that that universal god
peace that none of us you can tap into
it as deeply and as much as you need to
as an individual but because it's not in
a spiritual text it's not something I
can go to clergy for and be like explain
this to me you can only kind of get
guidance from other people who are going
through it and even then it's not really
alike you're right and I'm wrong because
we had a we democratically decided that
God shows up like this
it's still about your unique individual
thing that's coming out for you but
sometimes I'm like wait is this uniquely
mine or is this universal look I know
that don't exercise and eat whatever you
want isn't universal at least I'm pretty
certain it isn't but then again
thousands of people haven't tried it i
haven't tried letting go of what you put
in your mouth don't judge it like we
just let it go let go of what the state
of your health is and what the state of
your house is the state of your life is
and just love it where it's at is that
to me and these are again although these
are my universal truths to some degree
or my mic my secret to life bye
well if anyone did this they would be a
happier human being and I would rather
inhabit this planet with other happier
more fulfilled human beings but you
don't at every level we're gonna be
working on together as a society we need
each other because you can't hold the
pieces together I'm sorry is one single
individual
it is like everyone's walking around
with one puzzle piece - 7.5 billion per
piece puzzle and it's like on all of it
I'm the whole picture no you're not no
one's the whole picture you can't be
there are people who are the best at
faking they're the whole picture
thinking they're everything and they're
kind of when we're putting in power and
who are giving more more power and
privilege - but nobody has the whole one
people like me who can save or lacking
some stuff it's easier I think for us to
see that I know looking back at my life
pretty with my brain I always was like a
piece of the puzzle like it was like I
would what I wanted to be a writer I
never actually wrote like words on paper
I liked planning a world what are the
rules the characters but not really
characterization that made them human
and real it had like you know their
their shadow and their light but like
the logical piece of them like Oh a
vampire who like their um more like
their demographics and what that would
mean planet where there's three genders
right or three sexes and how do they how
do they interbreed there was literally
three it's like paper-rock-scissors
and like what does that do and then what
character so we need to come out of that
but the actual writing and again the
like humanization of the character is
the like kevin was calling making them a
complex character that you can actually
relate to not my strongpoint
and when you write a book you have to be
all of that here you have just be like
isn't this world cool
isn't this Wizarding World cool who
needs the Harry Potter story um but for
film and TV
nobody really writes the entire thing
that's not true for film it happens all
the time and then there's people but for
TV because it's come rapidly come no you
have a team of writers doing
like why don't we have a team of writers
doing it I don't understand or being on
group projects in school there was part
I hated about it and then part where it
was I could leave the pieces that I
didn't I wasn't very good at there was
usually somebody on the team who was
much better at it and then I would take
on what I what I could take on and now
that I've opened up to this saying this
magic this universe the source it's like
the right people do show up at the right
time you don't need to take on more than
you're willing to take on because
somebody else will and so how perfect
like although I haven't quite gotten
there yet a hundred percent of the way I
have a piece of the puzzle to the
solution I have a piece of here's what
the rest looks like where are the other
pieces right they go around where's the
edge piece we are gonna create it all
together and so I both know I'm exactly
who I'm supposed to be I'm not supposed
to be any different and at the same time
I'm like gee it'd be really easy if I
was better in public speaking only I
knew how to edit video only and so every
deeper level of learning isn't yeah you
should learn video you idiot okay what
it's it's like you're not supposed to
know it how many times I've sat down to
try to write out some grandiose white
paper you get like three sentences this
is not what my brain does it's supposed
to just hold the vision because the
vision is constantly changing
- and if I wrote it down then it might
become like not to be grandiose but like
religious texts in Darwin's theory of
evolution of like well Darwin didn't
agree with this Darwin didn't know
everything didn't really actually
understand the mechanics of evolution he
saw the world and thought up a theory
that could explain it that he happened
to look it look like he's mostly right
on but he didn't know genetics he didn't
know eugenics he didn't know you know
like all of the things that would would
come out of history and so he's not he's
like the grandfather of it but being the
grandfather doesn't know I think I'm
funny
I enjoy me sometimes other people don't
necessarily think that was a joke like
you know people have inside jokes I have
inside inside jokes like just just me
that was just for me that's why my guy
it's my God by whatever has to be
sarcastic like it has to be so
ridiculous what I am here to do then I
have no choice but to do it I have no
choice but to step into
I like there's this saying or something
in the self-help community like stepping
into your power and although it's not
something I'm gonna do one time I'd be
like I know I'm powerful that I can do
it's like a constant okay once I got a
little more a little more a little more
I'm regaining that peace every time I
regain it truly it's it stays and I get
into moments of power but it's to me
it's about love and acceptance it's like
can I love and accept myself right now
as I have and 99 percent yes but there's
always that 1% of there's always 1% own
cover just always like just oh where
aren't I accepting myself or aren't I
accepting other people and that is I
guess like the guide although I have
points here well get to eventually the
secret of life is to seek and I put down
happiness and then crossed it out
because again that's my thing like that
some people seeking happiness is not
seeking happiness in fact sittina
happiness leads to misery and allowing
life as it is including misery leads to
happiness
so seeking happiness isn't quite it it's
there was the same in this kids card
game oh this kid's affirmation card set
it was I'm perfect just the way I am and
I'm growing every day and I'm like yet
that kind of encapsulate can calculate
encapsulate sit that we are all growing
but to have a attachment to what that
growth looks like stops the growth
whereas a loving and accepting myself is
number one but also other people because
everyone's a reflection of you so when
I'm not loving and accepting to somebody
else it's because it's triggering
something in me I'm not loving and
accepting about myself and so the more
the one of the world triggers if the
world triggers me too much I go into
shutdown mode
and I think a lot of people didn't fight
flight or freeze when they're
overwhelmed and I definitely go into
freeze rather dramatically yeah and I
don't run point that was with it just
that that like seeking to truly love and
accept myself and I like again my
guidance is to be more selfish it's to
be more put your own oxygen mask on
before helping other people do what you
need to do be you're you're happy if you
don't want to go to something don't do
it do not do anything that does not like
spark your interest and your joy I don't
think that's necessarily everybody's
guidance but I needed that I needed to
because I was naturally the opposite I
was naturally a caretaker a giver of
everything of my being which is why I
have a partly why I have chronic illness
and so a lot of people chronic illness
have to learn the flip side look after
themselves that they matter that their
voice my voice always matters I've
always been a big talker but having them
whereas my guess is if you're born in
the opposite way if you're born selfish
and more let's say a narcissist
you're supposed to learn to be more
selfless right you're supposed to learn
how to take care of others not just
yourself and so a lot of times I think
the universe gives us the flip side to
learn it's like here's your personality
and you're here to learn the exact
opposite you're welcome and the irony of
that because it's not universal right
it's not everyone needs to be selfless
everyone needs to be selfish it's what
are you and how do you and so my guess
is not everyone needs to learn those
lessons not everyone who's born selfish
needs seller and selflessness and
everyone born selfless needs to learn
selfishness
that's my guidance and so you can see
patterns that repeat in people's lives
and they're weird they're weird patterns
like probability-wise they can't happen
but somehow they show up like the same
person getting struck by lightning five
or six times in my life I have someone
who I know who's been sexually assaulted
a ridiculous number of times and like
how do you keep encountering these
things like I don't understand
especially considering who she is I'm
like I don't understand but
I believe her like I don't because of
who she is of like I don't distrust fate
this is true but why do you like why is
the universe keep giving you these these
almost lessons and then someone who like
has an issue with relationships and just
kind of like not make it work past the
six-month mark and mines chronic health
problems like I don't know why and how
these exist I can't solve them I can't
solve them by myself and that's why a
lot of the solutions I've created in my
head are solutions that we can do
together I can't have I can't heal my
body
partly without healing the planet but
that's all whether conversation I can't
heal my body and understand what's going
on wrong with it unless there's other
people putting their information in the
system as well because I even if I do
something and I feel like it helps me I
don't know if it actually helped me you
need to actually have a trial you need
to have enough of a threshold of people
doing it to know what the outcome is and
it's the same with anything you meditate
you have to lighten it out of it yes
probably but having other people to
learn with can help you find your
learning style and so help you retain
information more having other people who
have your same taste in food can help
you you don't need to try every recipe
people like you can try the recipe
having health care that is
interconnected as much as we want it to
so our data is usable safe and washed
and usable is a something we can do
together and it's the only way to get
access to health really is to to know it
together and same with even this even
this religious God like magic entity
because its internal again you need
other people you don't need you don't
need to ever okay anything on the
outside for my experience but at the
same time sometimes I'm like um honey
only one experiencing this and no
because other people are too and if we
get the same guidance in a group how
amazing so more people following their
own unique guidance it interweaves in a
way it just were
like you can't control anyone else like
I was going to have I wanted to have a
conversation that came on with you make
a group conversation yesterday with
Heather and Eric on these four questions
and how we could use this hour in the
morning one day a week or every day to
help people with these four questions
what is something that this conversation
could look like and they're down to have
the conversation when I suggested doing
it during this time slot during Heather
was like I don't there's something about
going on YouTube that I'm not okay with
okay like you have to listen to your own
internal guidance even though that's not
working with mine but it is because I'm
like okay so we can how do I find what
works for both of us right do you want
to have the conversation yes or no can
it be recorded on YouTube yesterday
right so it's like finding the thing
that works for for her and me so we can
we can work together having the board
meeting for together tech and it's one
hour a week and it's evolved over the
course of the last five or six months
since Bentley and I found each other and
my brother joined the team as well that
instead of it being a tech cooperative
it's more of a projects coming together
and and figuring out the Omni Winn
solutions and it's I'm part of that it's
evolved and changed beyond what I could
I could imagine it to me but that was
not the point I don't remember
welcome back if it's meant to so follow
your own turn unique guidance which
means Elsi you start understanding that
oh that was it so I show up for the
usually if you have a team of people
working on something you show up for the
hour you take on since tasks you do them
over the next week and you keep doing
that but that although that is what we
do we take on one or two things for
either our project or together tech what
I have found is the most powerful is not
to attach to like let myself just run by
I'll let myself be like hey I draw this
idea and if I need to I can bring it up
in between the medians but generally
speaking I just show up a week later
like here's everything that happened in
the last week here's everything that
happened last week I don't know whether
I'm a source of chaos and that therefore
wouldn't work with everybody doing that
if you had five people on a board
and they all just ran with what their
heart and soul sat in between meetings
and then came back together and was like
this is what happened for me this what
happened for me I think that would be
awesome but it's definitely gonna come
up and get the conflict like Heather and
I had one like it was a new conflict to
people who are trying to come up with
like a way we can have a copper
generative conversation about these four
questions that will help the world and
you know she doesn't but she has an
internal guidance she doesn't want to do
YouTube videos right now yes okay I have
to go with your internal guidance and I
want you to do this and so finding your
unique guidance also allows you to see
that other people following theirs isn't
going to match your sometimes so it's
not going to be you have an idea that's
that's huge any other people jump on
board and other people don't jump on
board because it doesn't resonate with
them and so the more you follow your own
unique I need some more you're really
it's a lot other people to follow their
unique items and the more your guidance
truly becomes unique I think it does
start out a little more bland a little
more like eat healthy and exercise get
enough sleep do the things you know you
would do this is your internal mother
speaking do the things but that it
starts being like I have I still have a
hard time sometimes knowing whether the
voice inside is the voice or a voice and
it's often based on what the thing is
I'm doing if the thing is like low smoke
pot sometimes it is my addiction and
sometimes it actually is my higher voice
and I don't know it until I listen and
then there's you there's something
waiting on the other end or there isn't
but things like I mean it never tells me
to mess my health health up house up but
my personality does that just fine
sometimes it'll be like take this with
you and you go in the kitchen and
something no not right now
I argue with it but it's clearly happy a
cleaner house is probably better so like
that even if I'm wrong on it I listen to
the voice oh no my dish moved into the
kitchen so it's like the my
you mean of the the the course of action
and like I said argue with my guys all
the time so if it seems too hard I'm not
gonna do it if it seems because I can't
so it's like wait wait on that one I'll
get back to you on that and other ones
have been really hard and I've done them
I mean cutting my sister out of my life
a year ago was something that was
probably the hardest thing I mean
element the point where I can now
possibly reom rebuild that relationship
but it was absolutely what I needed to
do and I would never have thought it was
a stuff that needed to be taken before
that until it did need to be taken I was
like alright gotcha
this is a hard choice sister or project
I pick project in that moment and for
the good of her the cut of her child the
good of my child the good of everyone I
pick to do what I'm here to do to listen
to my own internal guidance and not hers
and I needed to let her guidance mean
next to zero for me and the only way to
do that was for what unfolded because
she was like an idol in my life
you've been subconsciously and that was
not healthy what I needed what I asked
for was for her to be kind to me when I
got was the opposite but it was exactly
what I needed it was like oh I have no
way agree with anything you just said
that was hugely mean but I needed you to
be mean I needed to see that you are you
that you are you have this shadow side
it has has hurt me my entire life
actually but I wasn't aware of it and
how much I have paid the price by
listening to your guidance and what
you're here to do and there's part of me
that thinks that's not even her guidance
but that's not for me to decide it's
like how can because my guidance is so
against the grain of society I he don't
exercise I eat what you want and do what
you want when you want to do it I have
not heard anyone else be like that is
the secret to life and I wouldn't again
suggest anyone else doesn't exercise or
eat what they want unless it comes from
their internal guidance and I don't
think it's a permanent thing
in fact I keep getting like no you need
to eat healthier it's like getting there
easy simple way which I can only figure
out together and not by myself but
following the map the map starts to make
sense when you start to follow it that
the answer to the four questions which
I'll get into in a second and then it's
simple I know I've been to talk about
this to like 40 minutes and I have it
it's like seek your highest good and the
highest good of others because in
seeking your highest good you're gonna
be seeking the highest doing good for
others like finding of what would
actually bring you the most what I say
happiness enjoy as long as it's not
hurting other people right so if what
brings you happiness is hitting puppies
over the head maybe don't do that but
like anything else that isn't if because
there are things that we've received is
hurting other people if your highest
order today is to dress gender
non-conforming and you go to the house
which no one's doing right now but you
trigger other people that might be a
negative thing in their life that day
might be exactly what they need but it's
not actually negative you're actually
hurting them you're not forcing them to
wear anything you're just count like
you're just existing and they're gonna
put judgment on that those things
absolutely go live your life but we also
have to own that that's have a ripple
effect in in society I know that me
living my life in my laksa days achill
way has a real impact on people and it
really rubs them the wrong way I eat the
neighborhood community who yells at me
when I'm beaten too loud even though I'm
quieter than the person who lives there
because she thinks I'm doing it wrong
she thinks I'm doing parenting wrong
doing life wrong I'll do it it's like I
can't I'm not I can't help cuz it's not
even if she came at me like that I could
respond like that right I could be like
well actually I'm okay with my life but
she comes at me from a subconscious I
hate you and therefore I'm gonna treat
you in this way and won't acknowledge
the hate at all so it's like well we
can't deal with it at that level we
can't see look at this level so we need
to just like not yoga what possibilities
open broader during quarantine regime
everything I mean what the world needs
is for enough people to heal and I don't
from kovat 19 I mean from society in
life to have the time and space to be
able to sit with their thoughts heal
from the emotions that they're
constantly trying to push down and that
is basically what has happened in
quarantine it's forced which is not the
greatest because I have having
experienced that on another level of
being forced to stay inside for my own
sanity and own sensory stuff but not
choosing that I wasn't like she'd be
really fun if I spent 90% of my time in
the house and every time I had to leave
it caused anxiety that sounds great
let's sign up for that but it ended up
happening that way and then I was forced
as like meditate meditate it's like no
so the universe gave me no option but to
basically sit and do nothing and that's
kind of what it's done to the entire
totem is did I do yeah it feels like
that doesn't it
for me it's day like 500 but like I said
the 10% that I wasn't staying at home
it's a huge 10% that I feel I like I
can't imagine people who have that flip
to work out 90% of the time and now they
have to be home 100% of the time because
I miss the 10% I was out my kid misses
that they're just she isn't a school but
I hate you miss is like going somewhere
being with people and doing and doing
those things we're finding new ways but
there's there's a lot of possibility of
endemic there's we're seeing what our
interconnectedness means that whether or
not you have faith in the system
the fact that other people don't have
faith in the system means they don't
trust and they can't take action that we
collectively might think is good like
stay at home and a quarantine because
they're like well this is fake you're
taking your fascist government and
stalling Phi G everywhere we're stuck
inside our houses and that might be true
as well but it's it's not we're stuck
inside our houses in a way we've
definitely never been before even if
this had somehow happened in the 80s or
90s we wouldn't have had the internet
and now that we have the internet on a
massive scale we're able to do things
like zoom with each other and come up
with new alternative ways even if let's
say this window over like actually
you're wrong we don't need to do that
everyone can emerge tomorrow the fact
that more and more people have really
truly gotten that a zoom conversation
maybe isn't quite the same as an
impersonal one but there are a lot of
positives to it that you don't have to
leave your house that you don't have any
contact with the virus that people like
me who couldn't leave our house anyway
can join in on it right people who don't
have child care even your kids can be
running around because everyone has that
right now it's like that we are
socializing differently which we don't
necessarily need to go back to the other
way I don't mean of course we're gonna
be and of course we're in the
restaurants of course there's gonna be
an events but could we also not bring
zoom could we also not bring for the
people that this works out better for
that we're different but there are
people who what we were doing before
work don't we better for them they were
way more social they liked the busyness
of life and other people for whom this
is gonna be a breath of fresh air oh I
get to take time I know I didn't know
how drastically impacted I was by
working full time until I had Matt leave
and I am the only person ever to ever
experience a birth like this where I was
in labor for four days and that was
exhausting it ended in a cesarean
section so I had abdominal surgery and
when I came home I never felt better I
was actually more energetic and had more
energy than most new moms really this is
hard I feel like a baby all day I was
like all I got to do is keep this baby
alive that's a whole that's all I gotta
do that it was I don't have to go out I
don't have to save the world I don't
have to go to work I don't have to do
all of these things that were like all
of these outside pressures I didn't
really realize we're causing stress and
causing an issue until you removed that
and gave me the one thing that everyone
stresses about everyone who this life
works fine then you give them a baby
they're like oh this is harder than I
thought there was something about it
that was much easier it was like all I
have to do is be with this baby I'm good
I can do this I can it's it brought my
stress level down whereas it brings most
people stress I broke my energy
requirements down not up and which I was
putting on myself this I'll take care of
the baby but the other things didn't
disappear
I allowed them to disappear and there's
a lot of that was a positive there's a
lot of negative that comes from having
all that a long time like you're you're
you realize not that I think we all know
were social animals
but how loneliness affects you and how
lonely you are whether you feel
connected on I mean for me the loneliest
I've ever felt is in groups of people
where I feel like I don't belong by
myself I don't ever really feel lonely I
feel bored and I feel like I'm not
getting enough socialization overall but
it kind of reaches the point where I'm
like and now I need it right like when
you get thirsty enough you're eventually
you're gonna like do anything to get
water if I shouldn't do anything to get
food if you're hungry eventually are
gonna sleep if you're tired enough it
never really gets to that point right
now I'm kind of in the flip side which I
don't work well in of oh I should be
contacting these people because they're
social animals and they're not used to
this and I want to talk to them but I
don't want to schedule it and have like
it's a should instead of a get to which
means it doesn't go well for me I'm like
I'm a list of people I should really be
having a conversation with at some point
in time because I miss them but also
it's more stuff on my to-do list it just
drains me so basically the religion this
one religion the guide the secret of
life just love yourself and accept
yourself and in so doing you end up
loving and accepting others because if
you don't then they're gonna reflect
back on you every shadow part of
yourself that you don't love and accept
and if you I think it works the other
way too but I I have not experienced it
that way where if you can truly love and
accept others for who they are that
you'll start to love and accept yourself
I experienced it in the other way where
once I was truly able to love it accept
myself and realize that my judgment on
other people was a reflection of my own
judgment on myself and therefore find
the places I wasn't loving myself and
add more love to it that I but you start
one and you get both you start with self
and end up loving others or you start
with letting others end up loving self
because you can't truly love all of
these people that have all of their
foibles and all of them talents and all
there and not realize that you're
lovable too like right they're all
worthy I don't mean love the people on
the pedestals I mean literally every
person like oh you're doing the best you
can you're perfect just the way you are
you're worthy just the way you are and
we all cut down days and we all kind of
suck sometimes and it's truly loving
yourself in those moments cuz you give
other people permission to make mistakes
and make amends you give yourself
Commission to make mistakes and men's or
you give yourself permission to make
mistakes and make it right and then it's
really hard to do that and not allow
other people to do that so you start
with one and you get you get the other
but all you and you don't wake up one
day and do it perfectly again I don't do
it in any way perfectly constantly I'm
like this person annoys me it's the
greatest gift because it's more for me
to learn but it's another level of love
and acceptance for myself and others and
then following my own internal guidance
is key because if I everything's
basically a binary option right we don't
do it or you don't do it if it agrees
with Society and I do it I do it right
if the choices do go to event a yes I'm
gonna go no I'm not gonna go and Society
says yes you should go I can cheat if I
if I go with society simply because
Society says yes you should go I've
already broken my internal guidance so
that's not actually I'm not going to
learn what I'm here to actually learn
because I listen to society and not
myself if I listen to my internal
guidance and it happens to match
society's awesome follow that if I
listen to my own internal guidance that
haven't said not that it's like no
actually you should stay home and even
if it's the wrong option everyone went
and turns out Oprah came and gave
everyone a free car to go it's still
because it was your internal guidance
that you followed there's still
something to learn there then following
societies cuz following societies is
simply going with the crowd and you're
not really gonna learn at the same level
as like oh I don't even know why I'm
doing this I don't know why I really
want to stay home but something's
telling me I should stay home and then
you listen and even if it's wrong
there's there's it's right because it's
there's something here that it teaches
you and again I don't know if that's
universally true but it seems to
definitely be true for me because when I
follow the human my sister was very much
my sister so that I could have someone
who I followed their internal guidance
and it poisoned me every step along the
way even though it was things that are
absolutely universal like eat well like
meditate like be a better person
thank you but like her version of a
better person being a Type A personality
doing these things and the more I
followed it the more I broke apart
because for her it works and for me it
basically it works for it doesn't work
for me that usually doesn't happen I
don't think most people have that in
their lives like oh if it works for
other people doesn't work for you but it
does because I needed to get to my own
internal guidance it's like and that's
basically it even the seeking the higher
good isn't just those two it's just like
I love yourself and love others and
follow your own internal guidance and
then you allow other people to follow
their internal guidance and the four
questions that I think help us to do
this because you don't these are
somewhat grandiose I mean loving
yourself and loving others is not easy
necessarily especially in our society of
this is what's okay and this what's not
OK society has a very specific path that
wants us all to follow and we go off of
it there is a cost to pay if it's your
own internal guidance it is almost
always worth the cost I have not yet
found one that is not worth the cost
including the like giving up my sister
for a year I was like yep I get it I get
now a year later I can see what what the
benefit was in the moments it only felt
like heartbreak and separation and then
the anger is came in but like it is
exactly what needed to happen and so the
four questions they can be more easily
answered that aren't and they get to
they get you to loving yourself in
others and following your own unique
audience I hope is Who am I
because the more you know who you are
the more you can be able to hear and
listen to your own internal guidance and
who are my people because that we are
social animals and this this is world is
better together so but being a member of
a group where you don't feel
accepted and you don't feel connected
can be the loneliest can be more lonely
than being alone so being able to find
your people is essential and that
doesn't mean again none of these are
grandiose oh now I know who I am
um done check because it's it's who am I
can be on every level if we taking
personality tests if that's your jam if
you like finding out who you are in the
quiet who you are in in stress times how
your body works how your mind works how
your emotions work it's any piece of
that just a little bit more and when
you're open to it every day all day
every human interaction every event is
here to teach you and even in this time
of copán 19 or we're quarantined like I
said I've been inside aside from the 10%
for years and although it's hard to
convey to somebody who hasn't there is
so much learning and beauty here some of
the best learning I have and this only
applies to some people can still do this
is to just go for a walk in nature and
I'm constantly being rejuvenated with my
purpose and my passion who I am and
arguing with my guides well I'm on these
walks I also come into contact with real
people in the 10% that bring out
conflict and just any any emotion in me
that I can deal with that so I'm missing
that piece but at the same time there is
a depth to events that happen that you
don't experience when life is fast when
you're just going from one event to
another when you're just like okay this
birthday party in this thing and then I
work full-time and I do this you don't
have time to find the depth of learning
in one event it took me a year to learn
what I need to learn for my sister that
wasn't because I'm a slow learner it was
because there were like layers and
layers and layers of it I had to process
it and there were like decades of issues
with us even though literally before
this event happened a week before I
would have considered her one of my best
friends and a week later I was like how
I've been dealing with you my whole life
in this manner and that's not really
true to the year it was like I said it
had you like the anchor
and hatred had to grow and then
dissipate in order for me to get to
where I am and yeah so who am i ik or my
people what is my purpose is just what
do I want to do right now in this moment
what's gonna bring me happiness what is
my internal guidance for like the next
thing does it need to be grandiose I'm
gonna save the world or maybe medical
doctor or I'm gonna be an engineer and
build the world's largest bridge it can
be those things but more likely it's
just your next step it's like the you
don't need a grandiose purpose because
your purpose is just to be you once you
figure out who you are and that you're
unique and you're with your unique
people just taking the steps that are
yours to take adds to the magic of the
god of the universe and the thing that
we don't understand and that's we were
like enough people who are tapping into
this because when you tap into this you
don't need it to look the same for
everyone else it's sometimes you do
sound like what do you mean that doesn't
work for you that way this is clearly
for it's like everyone's supposed to do
this and but that's your not theirs
right if I'm like well everyone needs to
I can't even thing ever nobody needs to
exercise it's poison for everybody and
then people are not exercising I'm gonna
feel really it confronted by that that's
my not theirs and so that just
beware that like when things arise all
right came out to the hour I just wanted
to reiterate what I said at the
beginning which is I guess I don't need
to recap what yesterday's was
yesterday's is we have a solution raid-z
on mental health and go back and watch
that it would have been day 10
possibility of pandemic tomorrow I want
to try life coaching injure in this
period of time so although that word
comes with its own set of God I tations
it basically just means I want to help
somebody listen to their subconscious
and around a question they have what
should I do with my life what you know
is this the right question I don't have
the answers for that but I have access
to the process that can help you answer
it with your subconscious and because
listening to your own internal guidance
is very much about listening to your
subconscious I want to showcase that
this works for everybody that if you're
willing to get in contact with your
subconscious
you get a message that's for you and
only for you and I can just help you to
code it so I will be posting the link
for participation as you have
participate on camera to be coached or
on voice then I will work through that
process with somebody who's willing to
do that so don't pick something you're
not willing to talk about live on camera
but anything that you are and then I
will which means today I need to go
through my coaching stuff because I
haven't touched in a few years but it's
it seems like a fun thing to try to do
train every one of these hours I enjoyed
the process of helping people I enjoy
the process of being of doing the
process myself which might be what I
will do I will do that that's what I
will do I will do the process myself
with me tomorrow on camera if no one
shows up to get coached and if somebody
does I will coach them coach seems like
the wrong word it really does it's like
I will help them I'll be there their
tour guide on the tour of their
subconscious if they've never
experienced that for the first time and
meanwhile I am trying to answer these
four questions I'm having conversation
hopefully with Erik and Heather on what
this process could look like with the
four questions working with the four
questions Bank showing them and so I'm
busy living every day figuring out who I
am who are my people who wants to come
help build the process of massive
collaboration what does that look like
to collaborate with a hundred ten
thousand a million people starting with
100 because a few of us can't figure
necessarily out one for ten thousand
without having those people to trial and
error it what is my purpose my purpose
is to create a world that works for
everyone and I know that's my purpose
because it's what my brain does when I
allow it to do what it's here to do when
I love myself exactly as I am and magic
starts a period of my life and I start
listening to my internal guidance
it's what's naturally unfolding my brain
wants to create a world that works for
me like everyone's but in creating a
world that works for me it creates a
world that works for everybody else as
well that's just my own internal thing
that needs to be nobody else's purpose
but the levels of that and how that
unfolds I would be silly to think I know
that because the more I attach to
the more it crumbles and the less I
attach to the path and just allow it to
unfold it happens and so that's why I'm
out doing it in public because I know
that it's gonna unfold it it's right
time and again I got to look a little
crazy until it does but it's already
unfold and it's already the right people
showing up at the right time and coming
into like it's magic happens and I'm
gonna show it cuz if we're gonna try it
in a little bit with somebody next
Laurel and then what do I need the
resources and that feels a little more
fragile at the moment because of the
whole Cove in 1905 urchin of gummy net
going to the grocery store our bulk
buying of creating the technology to
help do that side just doing recipes
recipe sharing and we're done now I'm
like actually we need to garden we need
to actually create the food because I
don't know if it's gonna come from
somewhere else but the whatever the
solution itself is is that a real point
that was one food social versus the
other food solution yes just that it's
evolving as copa90 that's was the
fragility of resources that I need
access to food that didn't change but
how I mission getting it has changed a
bit but then it's constantly an evolving
process okay right the hour
join me tomorrow for for coaching if you
want I will post the video for on the
YouTube channel with the link later
today so you can be one of the because
it's members first here really that I
will be coaching and there won't be that
long of a lineup
I don't think so probably and then if
nobody shows up I will coach myself
during that hour and you can see the
process that maybe the next time I do it
somebody will show up and do it with me
alright I will see you all tomorrow for
a coaching session
take care